{"transport":[{"level":"1","type":"transport","question":"I go beep beep! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚗 I have wheels."},{"text":"🚦 I drive on the road."},{"text":"🔑 You need a grown-up to drive me."}],"options":[{"label":"Car","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ball","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"2","type":"transport","question":"I carry lots of people on the road. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚌 I am bigger than a car."},{"text":"🛑 I stop to let people on and off."},{"text":"👧 You might ride me to school when you are older"}],"options":[{"label":"Bus","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Spoon","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"3","type":"transport","question":"I fly in the sky and take people far away. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🛩️ I have wings."},{"text":"☁️ I fly very high."},{"text":"🌍 I can take you to different countries."}],"options":[{"label":"Airplane","isCorrect":true},{"label":"House","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Banana","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"4","type":"transport","question":"I go on the water and carry people. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌊 I float."},{"text":"⚓ I need an anchor."},{"text":"🐟 I am bigger than a toy boat."}],"options":[{"label":"Boat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Hat","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Tree","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"5","type":"transport","question":"I have two wheels and you pedal me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚴 You sit on a seat."},{"text":"🚧 You need to balance to ride me."},{"text":"🪖 You should wear a helmet when you ride me."}],"options":[{"label":"Bicycle","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Table","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Book","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"6","type":"transport","question":"I go choo-choo and run on tracks. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚂 I have many carriages."},{"text":"⬛ I stop at stations."},{"text":"👧 I can take you to visit your grandma."}],"options":[{"label":"Train","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cloud","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Fork","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"7","type":"transport","question":"I help you go up and down in a building. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚪 I have doors that open and close."},{"text":"⬆️ I can take you to a higher floor."},{"text":"🏢 You find me in tall buildings."}],"options":[{"label":"Elevator","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Window","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pillow","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"8","type":"transport","question":"I am big and loud, and help put out fires. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚒 I am red."},{"text":"🚨 I have a siren."},{"text":"🧑‍🚒 Firefighters ride in me."}],"options":[{"label":"Firetruck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pencil","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"9","type":"transport","question":"I take you to space! What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🚀 I am very fast."},{"text":"👩‍🚀 Astronauts ride in me."},{"text":"✨ I go to the moon and stars."}],"options":[{"label":"Rocket","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Shoes","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cup","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}},{"level":"10","type":"transport","question":"I carry things but you push me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🛒 You use me at the shop."},{"text":"🍎 You put food in me."},{"text":"👪 A grown-up pushes me while you walk."}],"options":[{"label":"Shopping Cart","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Plate","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Clock","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"transport","icon":"🚚"}}],"food":[{"level":"1","type":"food","question":"I am yellow and yummy. Monkeys like to peel me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💛 I'm the color of the sun!"},{"text":"🍌 You peel my skin before you eat me."},{"text":"🐒 Monkeys go crazy for me!"}],"options":[{"label":"Banana","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Apple","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Carrot","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"2","type":"food","question":"I am white and cold. You eat me with a spoon. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"❄️ I'm very, very cold."},{"text":"🥄 You need a spoon to eat me."},{"text":"🍦 I'm a popular dessert."}],"options":[{"label":"Soup","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Ice Cream","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bread","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"3","type":"food","question":"I am round and red. I grow on trees. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🔴 I am the color of a firetruck!"},{"text":"🌳 You can find me growing on a tree!"},{"text":"🍎 Snow White loved me."}],"options":[{"label":"Apple","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Orange","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Grapes","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"4","type":"food","question":"I am long and orange. Bunnies love to eat me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 I'm a yummy vegetable."},{"text":"🐰 Bunnies can't get enough of me!"},{"text":"🧡 I am the color of a pumpkin."}],"options":[{"label":"Pea","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Carrot","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tomato","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"5","type":"food","question":"I am a drink that is white. Cows give me to you. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 You can drink me in a glass."},{"text":"🐮 I come from a farm animal."},{"text":"🍪 I am really good with cookies!"}],"options":[{"label":"Juice","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Milk","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Water","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"6","type":"food","question":"I am small and green. I grow in a pod. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🟢 I am the color of grass!"},{"text":"🌱 I grow in a garden."},{"text":"👪 I am often served as a side dish."}],"options":[{"label":"Pea","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Corn","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Bean","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"7","type":"food","question":"I am made of flour and you bake me. You can put yummy toppings on me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍕 I can be cut into slices."},{"text":"👨‍🍳 You can order me at a restaurant."},{"text":"🍅 I am a very popular dish."}],"options":[{"label":"Cake","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pizza","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cookie","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"8","type":"food","question":"I am yellow and come from a chicken. You can scramble me or fry me. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥚 I can be cooked many different ways."},{"text":"🐔 Chickens lay me."},{"text":"🍳 I am often eaten for breakfast."}],"options":[{"label":"Egg","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Potato","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Onion","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"9","type":"food","question":"I am a vegetable that's long and purple. Some people think of me as a fruit. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍆 I am a purple vegetable that sometimes tastes like a fruit."},{"text":"✨I can be grilled or baked"},{"text":"🌍 I am found in many different cultures and cuisines."}],"options":[{"label":"Plum","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Eggplant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Grape","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}},{"level":"10","type":"food","question":"I am made from apples and I am sweet. You can spread me on toast. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥣 I am often eaten with peanut butter!"},{"text":"🍎 I taste like the fruit I'm made from."},{"text":"🍞 I can be spread onto bread."}],"options":[{"label":"Jam","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Butter","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Honey","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"food","icon":"🍎"}}]}